# https://opentdb.com/api_config.php

question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In World War II, Hawker Typhoons served in the Pacific theater.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The United States of America was the first country to launch a man into space.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Space Station 13&quot;,  the station has a clown aboard it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
